okay this is gonna be a quick video okay
wait with all the [ __ ] dislikes
the dislikes where is it what the [ __ ]
is allowing you you pieces
of [ __ ] [ __ ] why do i get so many
dislikes
17.1 27 dislikes
look at these look at them all 8.6
dislikes
a hundred and thirty-eight just like
what the [ __ ] is wrong with you pieces
of [ __ ] [ __ ]
why do i get so many dislikes stop
[ __ ] disliking my videos
stop disliking them stop it
now look at this
look at this wait what the [ __ ] why am i
subscribed to this
unsubscribe now look why does he get
uh 80 85
86 80 but i get uh
8 27 26 what the [ __ ] i did nothing
this is better content of course bad boy
asmr gets confused because everyone
likes a bad boy
but you know what joe biden and possum
best one okay dear creators they're
hating on me for no reason why trump is
the worst president ever he
is he is let's just look at some of
these comments huh
[ __ ] racist as oh [ __ ]
i gotta close that these racist as
[ __ ] crackers okay
hello ma'am i'd love to defeat i'm not a
man
respect my pronouns okay
oh my god
oh my god there's so much haha this is
good satire satire
satire this is not
satire what the [ __ ]
well i'm not doing that this is so funny
i forgot to laugh and erase my memories
crin so hard and died
[ __ ] off oh yeah here we go exactly
thank you i can't say that name
cerventi rd
get off of mommy's ipad [ __ ] up
shut up you piece of
[ __ ] you
are a terrible person
and a drummer jumper trump is
nobody even cares you're the you're an
inspiration to all those antifa's
oh my god thank you i'll do that thank
you so much
oh that's so sweet genuine question is
this legitimate
is he being honest god i hope so
yeah okay well first off first off
create creationist
cringe i am
not believing in a phony
foam foamy god
god is fake and he
if [ __ ] if he
is real he is a
poc just in case someone doesn't know
per son of color
woman and yes
this is legitimate
there we go reply the ejection is not
over yet
it is over it's over it's over it's over
is is it over
now white
boy yeah it's over
it's over fighting for life kabbalah
will win and we'll make america great
again
i can't wait to see how he spells the
fourth grade slideshow presentation
about
claiming calling for trump complaining
about the election was called for trump
it was not called for trump you
are a you are a idiot
white person biden is
your president
and what the world
respects us now
thank god uh drop by this president you
know now the world
[ __ ] expects us okay
good i can't tell the satire serious
that slash trolling what all these
people think of a [ __ ] troll
i'm not [ __ ] trolling i don't even
i'm not gonna even reply to you because
you know what
i don't you don't deserve my replies
trump 2020
he lost it's lost
white boy he's gone
we are no longer
a puppet
for russia all right guys you know what
that's enough comments
heart [ __ ] off you know what no
okay that's enough that's enough
goodnight everyone
i hate you [ __ ] crackers