this is the worst day of my [ __ ] life
how can the republicans [ __ ] win if
blue [ __ ] virginia
all over the [ __ ] place you [ __ ]
dumb ass piece of [ __ ] [ __ ]
my [ __ ] god
lieutenant
governor
governor and attorney general oh great
now we're gonna have republicans all
over religion yeah virginia's [ __ ] now
[ __ ]
which is [ __ ] red
no it's not blue no matter who we voted
for joe budden
barack obama
and now we have
crackers
now we have glenn youngkin
oh i get a critical race fair is bad
so white supremacy's back i guess the
white crackers
the white parents had a vocaloid
supremacy now we have white supremacy
back
congratulations now we avoid supremacy
congratulations now we have [ __ ]
white supremacy and racism
rapid
all over the place because of white
folks
can't understand that critical race
theory is important
[ __ ] idiots
[ __ ] you [ __ ] you all [ __ ] you trolls
[ __ ] you [ __ ] republicans i [ __ ]
hate you all
[ __ ] you