there's a serious problem going on with
our nation
okay furry haters
they hate furries i can't believe this
i can't believe this you [ __ ]
imbeciles okay
how can you hate furries okay they bring
everything in life
they bring joy okay people tell me oh
foods are sexual they're not okay
they're not
sexual okay where's the sexual part
no they're not i can't believe you
okay i can't believe you [ __ ] you
[ __ ]
jew okay you've got the little [ __ ]
jew
okay boys are the greatest on [ __ ]
planet earth
shut the [ __ ] up okay these are the most
amazing people on planet earth
okay we gave 28 to charity okay how do
you feel about that
okay four years i don't see you giving
to charity
okay you've got damn [ __ ] jews
okay
what are you doing with your life huh
okay you have nothing you're living in
your mom's basement
okay meanwhile i'm living in my dad's
basement
okay wow wow i can't believe you you're
actually
gay okay you're seriously gay
okay and yeah you don't want a minute
okay
ass why do you hate your face okay it's
very wrong
okay please let me create
this is just like my dad he kicked me
out of his house
well he is going to he's going to kick
me out of this house
because
they can give him son what the [ __ ] is
wrong with you
okay and now my dad's leaving me
my mom found out
and my dad he put down
my boyfriend he was a good dog
he was a good dog why did he have to
i can't [ __ ] believe you okay
okay age doesn't matter in the full
world
okay [ __ ] you
believe you okay you guys are just so
violent and you're saying such violence
okay
it's just like my dad hitting me but
it's online
we're trying to get this to stop okay
it's wrong okay
okay okay so many people
are innocent okay
you freaking furry haters you just
[ __ ] you