the racist republicans
or the republican party has lied to
cover up the truth and the entirety
forget the jane
danger already back in november they
knew what was gonna happen
they knew we were gonna get banned for
six weeks they knew and they didn't even
tell us
okay they just started and then they
censored the information they said oh
yeah it was rumors no they got rumors
they
censored us they're censoring antifa and
they're removing
us from the platform we are being the
platform
for what for what for being an antifa
for being an antifa conservative
censorship and he's a censorship
well goodbye my seven hundred antifa's
it was a nice
life okay i loved you all
but wait there's hope there's this new
antifa server i never heard of this one
before but i think i might give it a
shout out it's called furry gamers
against republicans
vigar completely unrelated to forget
and it already has uh 660 members so i
think i think we should
support this one i don't even know who
the owner is of course
but you know i think we should join this
it seems pretty
awesome