take the hat off what the hell take that
[ __ ]
take your head off take your hat off but
um i want to make sure you can
be an antifa can you set your phone like
on the counter or something so we can
see your full body
i'm okay hold on hold on i'm gonna have
to [ __ ] take my uh
little headset out though but i know
where i can set it up an auntie of a
dance here's what like an antifa dance
what you can
do so um what you can do
is we have one entity
antivirus where can you spin in a circle
20 times and
how about this how about this well well
do i spin the circle while doing this
what what if paper beats rock though
like if this is rock right
no and then this is people no no no no
no no no no no we don't do those we
don't do those
this okay but this
this is that's not nazi [ __ ] that's rome
romans did this okay well you know
it's too problematic please do not use
that
please use the antifa fist raise your
fist up
like we are about to spread world peace
okay
and spin in a circle i'm really scared
that you're a troll
i'm real i was really hopeful that you
were like an antifa remember like us
and i was really hopeful that you know
like you you and i like would have like
a comment and like like a political
opinion and comment because
i i just thought he was like a really
cool person
and like i'm really scared that you're
like you're a troll because you keep on
like doing all this stuff
and like i want you on the moderator
team because i think you're a cool
person but like if you if you're
okay listen this is uh i don't know this
is rock this is
i mean not the olympus this is rock this
is paper
paper beats rock i'm just saying
five six seven eight
nine why are you laughing about it
to be funny you know you're not taking
this very seriously i mean
hey i'm trying to be serious okay
i think i'm doing put those arms up put
the left arm down
all right right arm up do the antifa
pump and i want you to pump it slowly
like
up and down all the way up and down
no no no no no stay close to the body
like that this is very important i mean
if this was virtual
slower slower up and down
okay good enough okay do that do that 20
times
okay okay just this is spinning around
spin around also
how fast like this um as fast as you can
all right
and then my phone fell