excuse me excuse me this is my public
service about skin for furry gamers
against trump please join the discord
server but this is my public service
announcement
please
don't be a [ __ ] mask hole wear a
[ __ ] mask wear one
wear a mask and if you wear them it's
not a chin guard
it doesn't go under your nose put it
over your [ __ ] head now [ __ ] over
your [ __ ] nose idiot
you don't do it like that you put it
like that and get an n95 mask or better
wear two and get the [ __ ] vaccine
this is a [ __ ] this is so important
we're in a global pandemic and you think
it's funny to uh [ __ ] around no um it's
not funny actually
it's not funny so please wear a mask and
thank you uh for this public service
announcement