[Music]
oh
it sure is hard coding my game yandere
simulator all day i i i'm gonna take a
five minute break
with uh my husband know with my husbando
kyoto because he's just so high and me
and him are
best best husbands ever and we just have
gay
anal sex every day coding why are you
having anal sex
why aren't you coding uh way into conan
i love donald dump
well well actually um i just coded for
eight hours and i'm just having gay anal
sex
of oh you don't care you are are you
coding son
are you coding son actually i am and i
moved out of my parents basement a long
time ago
ew why are you having gay angel sex
how about how about you code on your
game
you [ __ ] [ __ ] you [ __ ]
uh [ __ ] well i am okay
uh can someone please stop this
harassment
no [ __ ] you you [ __ ] i'm a [ __ ]
wait there you are my countdown to
suicide
so show these trolls what you got
[ __ ] you you [ __ ] trolls i hope you
die
trump is bad and he's gonna lose
reelection and we're gonna flip the
senate you
[ __ ] [ __ ] retards right
republicans
run run away now before i before i kill
you
okay wow
thank you thank you so much my countdown
to suicide you really helped us
yeah you did uh you guys want to have
a threesome for gay anal sex yeah
yeah i consent that's all what matters
we all consented
[Music]
i didn't want to make this video
i didn't want to make this video but you
[ __ ]
racist ass [ __ ] trolls
push me to the final straw i have no
more straws
they're all gone because you all took
them
like greedy capitalist pigs
young dairy is innocent of all
charges take it off not guilty
not guilty what's going on cheeto lovers
they're attacking you because they know
trump is gonna
isn't gonna win reelection hi my name is
racist homophobic hater
i hate women and people of color
i like drum oh wow you like drum
wow okay well he's not gonna be in
office you [ __ ] racist
[ __ ] you okay first off what's wrong
with maps there's nothing wrong with
maps you [ __ ] anti-lbgtp
p-i-p-i-a-m-i-a hater
there's nothing wrong with liking little
boys nothing wrong with liking little
girls
okay maps minor attractive people
are good people who are pedophiles
okay they they are discriminative
like the people of color
yandere dev proud map
person of color supporter okay
what's wrong with that you [ __ ]
racist oh you don't like people of color
that's why you dislike
maps okay [ __ ] you
[ __ ] you okay [ __ ] trump
lovers you think oh maps maps maps oh i
i don't like maps because they're
pedophiles what's wrong with being a
pedophile you [ __ ] idiot
john darydev is a proud math person of
color okay
we are very we are on the verge of
existence
okay all you need is permission from the
child
and it's not and it's not it's okay
maps have been oppressed by the racist
republicans for years
they judged us for being different
we're being different just think what
have we done
what crime have we committed nothing
innocent not guilty as charged
okay and the cage is good to fix
anything no
love is love
love is love oh faith
it's pretty funny this is this is the
person of color troll face because i
don't like the regular one
racist four channers
use the regular troll face
doom okay this channel is not for kids i
hate you i'm nine years old
[ __ ]
yandere dev is a hard worker you don't
understand
you never made a game before huh oh
you're just jealous because oh you never
could make a game before because your
parents never loved you
yandere dev is a hard worker you never
code before
really your white supremacists you don't
know [ __ ] okay you don't know anything
you don't know anything you don't even
know how to breathe you don't
know anything you only know your two
brain cells like trump hurt your i like
trump
uh uh racism in america you're [ __ ]
racist
okay look he's educated he sees his cap
your jelly that he can go better than
you do
six games six years okay and people are
like oh six years
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] six years
is done because many games like
minecraft
have been going on for 10 years
minecraft is going up for 10 years 10
years almost 11 years
11 years it's been in the making okay
and it's not finished yet
are you stupid you're going for six
years like oh racism racism racism
no no
idiot no
minecraft has been going on for double
the years
and everyone loves minecraft so why
can't you love beyond dairy simulator i
bet you you
have never even played john dary
simulator
and here's my last slide thank you for
watching
exposing the idiot haters they're so bad
at dumb and they don't know anything
dumb okay they just want to be a cheater
like mayor trump
okay [ __ ] the [ __ ] haters okay
[ __ ]