hey guys racist cracker here and welcome
to the channel
today we're going to be discussing why
racism is good
and community and sometimes playing
games where i'd be racist
i'm called the conservative because i'm
[ __ ] racist i'm a racist idiot my
community is smart and intelligent
and has love but i'm hateful like donald
trump and a [ __ ] racist
i hate black people and people of color
now if you couldn't tell that intro
was sarcastically making fun of a racist
name
conservative furry this man
has been racist against pocs
people of color for too long
it is time for someone to step up look
what was in his discord server
no lives matter you don't matter you
[ __ ] white boy
read that right there he says he's a
nationalist nationalists
are [ __ ] graces they're racists do
you conservative furry
you're a [ __ ] racist and it makes
sense you hate yourself
i hate myself i have committed unholy
sins i do not forgive
yeah that's being a republican you
[ __ ] white boy
white boy white boy i don't like you
you're not even hardcore you're just a
little where
where i believe in jesus this is the
cringe of the
creationist guess what jesus is fake
it's a [ __ ] fake
okay you don't believe in evolution oh
you think a little cool guy from the sky
uh did everything you were you're wrong
okay you idiot you idiot little white
boy okay
you haven't even seen my boyfriend's
dark side
okay you better watch out what you're
saying white boy
what the [ __ ] is going on with my
channel why are my views and revenue
going down nearly fifty percent
are people unable to pay your in your
ability to watch youtube because you're
second grade depression
no cracker people want to watch your
shitty videos because they're [ __ ]
[ __ ] and they found out your phrases and
you're an idiot troll face
i'm afraid to say but being an artist is
really dry it's his way to get money on
the fly in an extended hobby
it's [ __ ] you [ __ ] you [ __ ] being an
artist
is a job and you're just a lazy little
crap
white boy white boy okay and i hate you
here's this cry baby white boy crying
about
oh a little quicksand oh i'm gonna die i
just sank through
oh this looked me at the bottom too
hey white boy arty no one cares okay
no one cares anyways here's my video
destroying mr racist conservative furry
for being racist about this
racist little white boy this little
white boy named conservative furry
how dare you call yourself a [ __ ]
conspiri
how dare you
he reviewed he reviewed my discord
server
you know and i think it's absolutely
disgusting
disgusting i don't even you can't even
use little zainax he's a gay
furry man and you cannot use he's being
left
okay and you're [ __ ] racist
look look where he is three gamers
against trump
my server it's mine
and even worse he wanted my channel
and he said my videos are [ __ ]
hours and hours of work were put onto it
[Music]
the real joker you are you are you
are you're the joker let's go to the
about section
whoa hello i can't even read this
garbage
you can't read yeah
[ __ ] racist okay no no no no let's
let's move on let's see this video this
is his
my prediction trump will win 2020.
let's see this that trump's going to
take pennsylvania
michigan and arizona wrong
wrong zero percent you get a zero on
your test
you're wrong dislike dislike
you're wrong pencil trump didn't get
arizona he didn't get michigan he didn't
get pennsylvania he got nothing
nothing he didn't even get georgia you
dumb cracker
cracker you were so wrong you got zero
you got a zero you got a [ __ ] zero
because you're an idiot
you're not hardcore i'm hardcore have
you ever been to an antifa rally
you know the people who i fought people
you would never dream of you could fight
you [ __ ]
idiot bited wins because
you and the crackers can't get him to
win
okay and now let's move on to this video
this video
is
makes me so angry rt night tv
he is not guys on your youtube channel
i want you to apologize to all my
discord members
in that video i want you to renounce
you calling yourself a conservative he
is a conservative he's [ __ ] racist
he's a racist cheeto nazi he is none of
it
i want you to fully admit that you're
part of antifa he is not an mp
he is not an antifa rtd tv
youtube [ __ ] is not an antifa he is
not with us and i will stop
he is racist
disguise as them to spy just please
listen no
no forgive you
here's a lot of their tactics don't you
yeah please i'm sorry
we have no tactics
stop talking to me okay i'm being
serious
you know how hard it is i grew up poor
i grew up [ __ ] poor okay
and i worked so hard as an antifa
furry i'm for the booze y z i'm for
i'm i mean i'm not for the bouzou z i'm
for the working class of america
not america the whole world and this
[ __ ] cracker
this [ __ ] racist little white boy
racist little white boy
needs to say oh ow um you're an antifa
so you're the racist or antifa you're
racist
[ __ ] you