michael goldstein rogers
what what what do you want mom
i've been getting calls for the past few
days oh don't answer don't
mom don't answer them don't answer no
don't don't answer them okay and it's
called
michael if they call when michael
ratchet still answers my mom
no you want me to answer them no no no
no okay mom it's nothing illegal okay
it's just i it's just i'm on discord
and i'm on the internet and then it's
just getting
this poor boy 13 years old what have you
been doing
about what about who i don't know it's
not about you it's about me i don't even
know
listen mom just let me deal with this
stop okay i
really wanna believe you i really wanna
believe you i really wanna believe
you're always on that god damn [ __ ]
computer
okay yeah i have a lot of fun okay it's
not like you [ __ ] force me that
[ __ ] shitty walmart job where i have
to be
a capitalist wage [ __ ] i don't want this
[ __ ]
but i still haven't put it on disability
for over eight
[ __ ] years yeah because i'm disabled
i have five [ __ ]
autism you [ __ ] roar you fat [ __ ]
piece of [ __ ] [ __ ] you
okay i have to deal with this [ __ ] what
do you mean
what do you mean it's my superpower are
you [ __ ] piece of [ __ ]
[ __ ] you mom you such a [ __ ] [ __ ]
thank you don't you ever say [ __ ] you to
me [ __ ] you [ __ ] you
[ __ ] you [ __ ] you goldstein
rogers what
i'm taking away your internet proof no
are you [ __ ]
mom i'm 28 [ __ ] years old you can't
do this [ __ ]
twenty-eight [ __ ] gears only you
can't even get complained about for one
week
stop [ __ ] yelling at the white people
stop [ __ ] yelling at the light
i just don't like them your job is
supposed to cast you out your job is
supposed to be nice to them and you know
what we've gotten three calls
three calls because you've got three
people god who knows i was gone oh my
god
oh my gosh you know you have any issues
you call us for this family
daddy [ __ ] that she's becoming family
people
what are you talking mom why
why do you care why do you care why do
you care how i treat white people
it's not like you're getting the
treatment
mom oh what
mom i got this job because i love you
i care for you i got you this job
because i just want to see you succeed
i just want to see you get some goddamn
work experience
and you can't sit on my [ __ ] computer
eight
hours a day go doing god knows who what
for the last eight [ __ ] years all you
do
is just sit on that computer why why
michael
michael what are you called about
what are the calls about why am i
getting calls from friends
but why should i tell you you're just
gonna take away my [ __ ] internet
well maybe if i take away your [ __ ]
get to that people will stop calling me
calling you a goddamn pedophile
you have to do this [ __ ]
phone you piece of [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] you
what did you do michael what did you do
there is this guy okay his name was andy
his name andy okay and um
well he's 13 years old and uh
he wanted to talk to me okay
mom mom do you want okay
and this is andy 13 years old like
everyone else has been telling me
that's his role play age
that's his role play age mom okay it's
his friend
his role play age okay role play what's
the role play
role play no it's like pretend it's like
patty cake it's all it's fake okay
i don't know real age
old mom mom i'm lonely
mom
if it's a role play a play role or a
[ __ ]
[ __ ] i don't [ __ ] i don't [ __ ]
know okay
listen what what do you want mom
i'm taking your internet access away for
one day
one day oh no
[Applause]
you are what are the most white-ass ass
sons i've had others being like this do
you see your brothers being like this no
they graduated out of high school and
got a job
they graduate out of high school he got
a job
i've been keeping you in my basement for
the last
past 10 years and you won't even get a
[ __ ] job
mom okay
um what do you want me to say i'm sorry
i have high functioning autism i can't
control it
i can't get a job i want you to lower
the internet use
no you do good on walmart
no i don't want to go to walmart two
days a week is too [ __ ] much
it's two days a week it's two days a
week i go there
six days a week somebody could keep us a
float do you know how hard it is to work
a walmart job and keep a house do you
know how job it is how hard it is
i try so hard i try so hard and having
another mouth of feet doesn't [ __ ]
help me either
mom why are you being so mean this is
like child abuse
i'm your child you're
28 years old yeah
okay you know what no i love you [ __ ] me
bless the cps took you away
mom why do you care about me
you want me to be taken away so you
don't care about me you want me dead
you're [ __ ] around with 13 year olds
on the internet i watch
it all play
it's fake it's fantastic i want you all
i want you off with a computer i want
you to get a girlfriend
i want you to work your face out and
actually i want you to work three days
not two days
no no my labor's being stolen
[ __ ] you [ __ ] you