frustration
frustration andrew yang is being
discriminated
by the lame stream media and the jewish
mafia by trump's uh
drone russian bots so much racism for
the person of color
are you [ __ ] for real really america
i probably got pass over racism but
apparently
we still own slaves slaves
slaves to the system we're in chains
this poor asian person of color is being
in
chains
[ __ ] you and [ __ ] donald trump
i wanted by a thousand dollars but the
mainstream media and the establishment
media
they had to ruin it look look at this
look at this
32 32 19 15
7 5 3 but they don't show andrew yang
he had more than beta or a rock
what the hell [ __ ] cnn
cnn is blacklisting andrew yang
and your gang um make america great
again
they're scared let me show you donald
dump
is scared of andrew yang in the race his
racist
rhetoric
and here's another thing don't walk
run productions racist against people of
color says donald dump
wall is okay he's racist against
mexicans are you [ __ ] for real you're
racist against mexicans
who's gonna clean your toilet then who's
gonna clean your toilet
he makes up lies he says that the
trickle up
economy can't work he are you
[ __ ] for real okay you [ __ ] white
[ __ ] male
person okay you hate person of colors
okay look at this
hair hitler
republican flag okay
look at these poor mexicanos they're
just trapped in the cage
donald dump let this happen [ __ ]
don't walk run protections
look and then look at this quote
i am okay with dyed children
they are mexican so they decided
make america great again clearly donald
trump is saying this he's saying this
he hates america
he hates america my frustration
they were so bad like the black people
and people of color
the people of color
and then and then the main the
mainstream media the mainstream media
try to say andrew yang andrew yang
did not suspend his campaign are you
[ __ ] for real
first off injured gang campaign would
give freedom
to and not to the racist rich people and
they would have lower money
people of color people of color
would vote and they would destroy donald
dump
in 2024 donald trump would finally be
over if we had andrew gank
every would get money and the rich
does not get to keep it all they all get
to keep the money they steal all the
money the one percent jewish mafia
okay they all come from israel and they
steal all their money what the [ __ ]
no more climate can't change because
people don't have to buy racism from the
one percent
okay we can all have collective it okay
we we would all be rich
and then they try to say we didn't hit
he hit hit
the 2 million uh milestone oh really
really
really mainstream media hacks really
yeah okay okay racist and then the mbs
msnbc and and nsbc
is trying to say this here's the graph
racism
a hundred percent wait i mean
the the laugh is backwards okay do the
young talks
the young talks are very on racist
the sexism is very very low
okay this is the scrap is fake okay
however
the young tux is very is very homophobic
they hate the homophobes i mean they
hate they hate the gays
but they're very on on drunk
but msnbc they're drumpers
they're homophobic they're sexism
they're racist not like the young talks
cnn cnn is homophobic
they're racist and sexist hail trump oh
yeah
and then rachel mad cow [ __ ] you reach
your back how you [ __ ]
pig [ __ ] you you [ __ ] cow [ __ ] you
andrew gang choice everyone
and then the lame stream media lined
about the new hampshire polls
name yes please name one person who
didn't vote for andrew yang in new
hampshire
really really can you i bet you can't
but you can't name one person that
didn't vote for ranger gang in new
hampshire can you
name one i can't name one that didn't
vote everyone i know voted for andrew
gang
okay look at this lame stream media i
know this is very fake
this is i found a real one he actually
got a hundred delegates
okay this was fake by the lame stream
media okay
yang i'm suspending my campaign
yang gang you know what i'm gonna
campaign even harder
he never suspended his campaign [ __ ]
he never gave up his delicates
we live in a society that teaches women
not to be careful to be raped
by instead of teaching men
not to rape
thank you all thank you all for this
amazing slide thank you
all uh uh thank you thank you so much
thank you for 50 subscribers
thank you