i can't wait to tell all my new friends
about night the hacker when i go to
paraplegic cross country
meeting tomorrow okay i don't want to
get arrested
oh wow oh i'm sorry i'm not gonna i'm
not gonna tell anyone that disabled
cross country
how can you do cross country if you
don't have legs
for real i thought i told you so many
times
how could you do after you how could you
run if you don't even have legs
i told you it was paraplegic
across country okay how does that even
work are you [ __ ] through
okay explain it for nightmare okay i'll
tell you
the whole story about oh my god i can't
stop
crying it's okay you'll get over
cause i promise you damn i could i know
i know i'm in a lovely accepting i'm in
an accepting community i know i can do
this
so i'm going to come out to you all
about paraplegic cross-country
okay i got it sorry i got it okay
i'm gonna cry stop crying
so what i do i go in my wheelchair
my mom takes me and we go to the track
we go to the track and i have to like
pull the wheels
go all the way wow