guys little husk here and welcome to a
cringy tech talk video
i set up this account just a couple days
ago
it's going to be absolutely
cringe-worthy and
i just wanted to make this video to
introduce myself
but i also wanted to say that you know
people have been telling me that i've
been cute
i'm here to dispute with that fiction
what the [ __ ] is so
cute about this [ __ ] nothing
i'm [ __ ] disgusting i'm sorry it's
just the truth
okay you can do a lot better than my
[ __ ] ass okay
that's the fact hey guys
little husk here and welcome back to
another video today we're going to be
talking about why
the entirety of the school system and
education in itself is [ __ ]
the reason why is because education
learning is learning new information
that you didn't know before
not taking some tests based on things
you've already learned
okay that's just called copying that's
as simple as that
guys chelsea here and welcome back to
another video today we're going to be
disproving veganism as an idea
so veganism is stupid for multiple
reasons
number one because the human body needs
a balance of both meats and vegetables
number two these animals are
already being killed so why are you not
eating the meat
yes it is a problem if more animals are
being killed than are being produced
but what's not a problem is eating
animals at all because these are already
dead so i don't get why you're not doing
it especially if it's good for your body
to balance out the meats and the
vegetables thank you very much have a
good day
today was crazy so i wake up
and i'm thinking today's gonna be a good
day and i was
gonna you know apply for a job today
so that's what i was gonna do so i was
like all right
and so i start the day by trying to go
under my bed just to like kind of clear
it out a little bit
and then the exercise machine that i
have against my wall nearly falls on me
and pretty much nearly crushed me to
death
the next part is i basically grab
everything i need to go
i go outside i'm looking on google maps
on my phone
and i'm walking through 90 degree heat
my feet are starting to hurt and i'm
sweating like
absolute madness and i was pushing
further and further to my destination
and i felt like i was literally dying
literally by the time i got back
to my house my heart was beating so fast
i could swear
that i was dying hey guys husk here with
another video
and today we're going to talk about the
lgbtqia plus community and what i have
problems with them for number one is
definitely the flag
i don't get why they have to fly a flag
just because they think they're special
they're not special at all it's like if
i were a conservative or a liberal
according to political ideology i
wouldn't fly the flag
that'd be stupid as hell so
imagine you're me and you walk
to work look at this this
in the middle of the goddamn river
like what the [ __ ] am i supposed to do
jump in the [ __ ] middle of the river
that's where that's that's interesting i
didn't know i was a [ __ ]
fish my final problem with the lgbtqia
plus community is that encourages hate
against straight people
specifically in the community it has
everything it has asexuals it has
transgenders it has
people that don't identify as anything
non-binary
but you'll notice that they don't
include straight in there why
because it's not a community of
acceptance if it was it would have
straight people in it
think about that it's a community of
hate against straight people
hey guys welcome back to another
[ __ ] video
i'm little husk my second video on the
lgbt community was removed
for pointing out a definition on google
i said that another problem i had was
that
if you look up the word gender dysphoria
on google and you specifically read the
definition it says
gender dysphoria is a condition where a
person experiences discomfort or
distress because there's a mismatch
between their biological sex and gender
identity
this is known as gender identity
disorder
gender incongruence or transgenderism
it's literally a mental illness
and for pointing out that fact and
something you can search up
i was unrightfully censored because
these people
are so [ __ ] trigger-happy that oh
we're just gonna censor
anything anti-lgbt these people are
pushing mental illness for god's sake
this video is a response to the trump
song and the idiot who made it
biden is a [ __ ] fake ass catholic
he lied about his religion just like his
mental state
the dude is [ __ ] old can't even climb
stairs
he is about as stable as our economy
he stole the election could not get a
vote
his rallies were as small as his brain
capacity
his policies are bad defund the police
open borders and knock downs plus the
new great depression
his constant racist [ __ ] and he is
anti-gun
truth is he is about american as beijing
baby you are the most amazing kind and
caring person i will ever know
you are worth all of my time and energy
you're not only one of the best
girlfriends i've ever had
you're literally a soul mate i'm always
glad to hang out with you and i always
want to because
i'm always thankful to be with you i
would never want to hurt you for you do
not deserve it
you are special and beautiful in every
single way
and i will tell you every day until i
can't anymore
i love you eternally these are things
according to my girlfriend
that are wrong with her it is a list
according to her
annoying clingy short hated bad acne bad
nose
horrible birthmark she's small has
mental problems bad teeth weak slightly
colorblind and dyslexic
you know my response to all of that is
here's my response
to that absolute garbage
if you gave me the chance i would take
it it's a shot in the dark but i'll make
it
go with all your heart you can't shame
me when i am with you there's no place
i'd rather be
directly the words i would sing to you
and i don't do this [ __ ] for anybody
because number one i'm cringy as [ __ ]
and number two you're the only person i
care about enough
to do this for okay
i literally spent the last couple
minutes
practicing because that's how bad i am
at this
if you think you're anywhere half as bad
as me
you gotta be joking me
i'm annoying cringy
fat and
i have asthma and i'm autistic
give me a [ __ ] break give me a break
and every time you say that nonsense you
know what my response is every time
you're perfect the way you are because
when you say these things about yourself
i immediately am ready to counteract you
every time you have to go here's
directly what i say
here is exactly the line i said to you
yesterday at 2 35 pm on discord
no matter how many times i get beaten
down or how much it feels like things go
wrong
you