hey you what are you doing
no i can't sleep again oh honey i'm
sorry
me
i just got up to head to the bathroom
and realized you weren't in the bed next
to me
oh come on baby come back to bed
it's too late oh
severe case of insomnia poor baby
is anything worrying you do you want to
talk about it
oh
oh darling i'm sorry
no wonder you can't sleep you poor thing
can i help in any way can i make some
tea
or hot cocoa that only seems to do the
trick when you're having
trouble sleeping
you already have a drink okay
then i think maybe heading back to bed
and trying again is a good idea
come on come with me
yes and bring your glass of water with
you cutie
come on i'll drag you back there if i
have to
that's it sweetness okay
you get in here with me i'll keep you
nice and snug
that's it come here come in close to me
baby
let me wrap my arms around you just
nestle under my chest and i'll hold you
nice and tight
there we go warm enough honey
good
just relax sweetheart relax into me
let me take care of you okay
baby this totally counts you're stressed
and suffering from insomnia
not deserve something looking out for
i want to help you feel better if i can
he looked pretty upset when i found you
in the living room
yeah right because nothing is notorious
for keeping you awake at 3am
i'm sorry to tease you it's true
sweetheart
this is the fifth day in a row now that
you haven't been able to sleep
getting kind of worried about you if
this doesn't get better we might have to
take
you to a doctor
well i i don't know
maybe they'll prescribe some sleeping
pills or send you to a sleep clinic
but if there are remedies we can try
it's worth a
shot right
oh baby i'm sure it's nothing serious
you've been under a lot of stress lately
that beautiful brain of yours has been
putting up with more than it can handle
at the moment
it'll pass we might just need a helping
hand until then
that's all yeah
are you sure you're okay sweetheart you
seem anxious
oh yeah like a tightness in your chest
okay that's all right honey
i just want you to slow your breathing
down for me okay you're okay
you're with me now
no you're not gonna have an attack baby
i promise
anxiety is horrible i know but breathing
slowly and
deeply else just hold on to
me okay
you're in our bed you're safe in my arms
now nothing bad is happening
i promise well good girl
you're doing so well nice
deep breaths in for three
out for three okay
that's it it's okay baby it's okay
there that's a little bit better
that's it just hold on to me baby i'm
here
easy baby easy
that's it you're okay
i've got you you're safe and sound with
me
okay just focus on my voice
my hands are stroking your hair
squeezing you close to me
that's it nice deep breaths
just try and let everything fade away
from your mind
imagine some still water and some trees
gently swaying
place where everything's calm and quiet
that's it baby don't think about
anything else
you just let yourself drift off to sleep
i've got the rest okay
you're okay just let it all go
hold on to me i'm going to be here until
it's all over
yes i promise
just keep breathing for me nice and slow
good girl you're worth so much baby
you're a wonderful person capable of
equally wonderful things
no matter what your anxiety tells you
you're so loving and
kind and gorgeous i just love you so
much
you're creative and quirky and you
procrastinate a lot
but that's okay because it's part of who
you are
all parts of you are worth loving
no matter what you might believe and
your mistakes and shortcomings
but you're also the growth
the knowledge and maturity you hold