wow wow
donald dump has taken this too
far donald dump i had to make this
presentation
to show you donald day dump
okay no longer donald t trump okay
he's taking it too far okay
as an atheist i gotta say trump
can't he cannot be president
this is awful he cannot be reelected
here's my reason first he hates
mexicans
he said mexicans are rapists
he said all black people are lazy
that that's your average donald dump
supporter look at look at these look at
these cages
trump is putting in him he put mexicans
in nazi camps
he's hitler because this is like
the jews okay are you [ __ ] for real
donald dump wow
wow donald dump
i can't believe you you
[ __ ] white male
of course you're a straight white male
and he only helps rich white men
no one else benefits from donald dump
he doesn't care about the blacks
he's so racist find one black person
that likes donald dump
okay there they he's so
racist look at this look at this this is
why i love reddit so much and i go on
reddit all the time
company dumpity out on the wall
trumpety dumpity made america fall
because he is literally hitler
[ __ ] donald dump anyone who likes
donald dump
is gay here's here's what i like to see
no no
trump no
[ __ ] you donald trump he hates gays he
is
furries and transgenders
he doesn't let transgenders in the
military he you makes them force to use
our social contract
gender what the frick
[ __ ] [ __ ]
he wants to ban gays from military and
he hates them
because he's a cis white scum male
he hates the lbgtqia community
because they are smarter and has love
not his go bigger
look at this here's another reason we're
at the laughingstock of the
world look
ow wow his hair looks like
corn
and look at this jimmy kimmel destroys
dump donald thump okay look
watch this youtube video look
donald dump this is donald dump and
jimmy kimmel
so i'm so angry and look at this
donald dump wow this is really donald
dumps
real thing i can't believe it but once
you watch
this fourth claim you you you'll be on
that donald trump is a big fat
bully and he hates trans gays
and anyone that's not a white scum male
look at this he's been so [ __ ]
roasted
trump is the most nazi racist homophobic
and [ __ ] hate him he's so
[ __ ] bad everyone knows he lies and
hates black people on queer
lb gt iqa plus people okay
he he thinks there's two genders what
the yeah [ __ ] you
okay trump more like dumb
it's a [ __ ] okay
trump supporters evidence
yeah yeah look at this on him no one
likes you
donald dump no one like old dump
no one no one likes you okay donald dump
okay
you you you you're just gay okay
you hate you hate everyone oh so guys
that's my
slideshow i hope you enjoy
showing that donald trump is a racist
white scum
male and he he should
um so guys see you later