and then i heard that you went on
vr chat with him and what happened there
well he blocked me in a corner
and he wouldn't let me move and
he took me to the sex room the sex room
wait wait wait wait you're 12 and he's
17 taking you to the sex room
so i've been hearing some heavy
accusations coming from you
uh mrs meredith you know uh would you
like to state your age for the record
um i'm 12 years old you're 12 years old
yeah okay and uh i heard you've been
getting messages from a man a man called
conservative furry is that correct
yeah and at the time his username was
like little hus x
i think okay so uh what happened
in between these messages uh what
happened and i heard there was voice
chat so well what were happening these
weeks yeah
well he repeatedly asked for
me to turn on my camera um
with no clothes on you know he was
looking forward to no clothes
the top and the bottom off those
you wanted your clothes off on discord
call not even underwear
like i don't know how i felt about that
wow
and how do you how do you feel how do
you feel uh about
about him doing that to you well
i don't i felt uncomfortable and i was
scared at the time
because i he told me he was gonna dox me
if i didn't do it
and then so you're saying you basically
got virtually raped
i did you got invited on discord
yes believe all women hashtag me too
thank you so conservative furry
virtually rapes woman
who not even a woman you're 12 years old
you're 12 years old
i told him i was 12 too do you know he
still did it
you know how old he is he's 17 years old
17 you hear that everyone's 17 years old
17 year old talking to a 12 year old
okay asking it to take off our clothes
okay
conservative furry wants to accuse me of
being a pedophile
please explain this believe all woman
believe all woman
woman believe their story okay
and before that i can't tell him i'm 12
i'm 12.
stop but he said i'm gonna dox you
and tell your family about this
and so i went in there and they started
groping me virtually with his virtual
vr hands he virtually groped you
with his virtual hands he groped you
yeah what a disgusting [ __ ] monster
what a monster virtually groping a woman
in vr chat
disgraceful conservative furry
disgraceful
and it should be legal to like children
all you need is permission from the
child
and it's not pedophilia you think
being different should put you in a cage
love
is love