hey what's going on guys so today i'm
going to teach you how to get the among
us hack the dev secret code
every time and among us okay
this is every time and this is no human
survey i'm not scamming you this isn't a
scam or whatever
this is how to get it every time and it
works if you've seen it right now
it works it works for real okay this
isn't a scam i found this
you know it took a couple hours but it
worked it works
so if you appreciate my efforts please
like comment and subscribe that's all
you have to do just like it takes a
couple of seconds just go under there
and then just press the button then go
back to this video i mean you're
watching it right now
so anyways this is how you get
an imposter every time with the secret
dev code
okay so this was left in the game files
and
it recently was re-enabled by accident
so
you only have a limited time to do this
so watch carefully
so this matters exactly and sometimes
you know
sometimes it has glitches but you have
to do it exactly how it is so you want
to go to account
okay and you want to do change name okay
and you want to change it to capital m
c t s capital m
c t s you hear that no i need to re
repeat
for the whole class okay i think i don't
need to so you need to press confirm
okay okay and then you want to press
go offline okay this is important
okay and then you want to spam the
online spam online now
now spam it now spam it now now now now
okay keep spamming keep pressing it
okay okay five
four three two one account
play as guest play as guest do it now do
it now
okay and now we're playing as guests
okay but here's the thing we're playing
as guest as
mcts okay
so now we're halfway there if you did
this congratulations
now you're playing as a guest and you're
not supposed to be doing
this you shouldn't be as mcts as guest
you know
it should be a completely random name
but now you're in
you're halfway in now there's one other
step
the thing is this has an encryption code
so if you do this you're not going to
get the hacks you're not going to get
the imposter every time
if you do this so what you need to do
now you want to press this
and you want to go to your browser
safari it could be on your computer
and this is for the encryption process
so it can be processed by our server
ends
so you want to double tap out of here
and you could this could be firefox
this could be uh uh safari anything or
you can do this on your computer
and you need to type this exact url
exactly
okay exactly no mistakes here this is
not a time to make mistakes
you need to type that exact url write it
down now
that exact url that's the url you need
okay
f e a t u dot
r e slash f g a t
it needs to be exactly that or this will
not work it needs to be exactly
remember if this doesn't work maybe you
you got to go back and do a couple of
steps again
because this should work if you do the
exact way
it's attended to so you get this website
and you don't have to read anything
just sign up you need to sign up okay
sign up so put in your email you know
uh you need to verify this email so make
sure
this is your real email you really use
okay
so i'm gonna put my email
this is my email
okay and then just select the palm trees
this is pretty easy
you know and then you got to create a
password
okay well i'm not
it don't have this bad of a password as
me
but it's fine for now
okay first name michael
rogers and sign up sign up don't save
okay now enter your zip code date of
birth
i'm just going to skip that for now and
now
now this is the important step this is
the important step
now you need to do this survey do this
survey you need to complete
at least three surveys and it's easy
it's easy
once you complete these three surveys
the humongous hacks will be unlocked
and you can go online okay so i'm going
to quickly do the survey discovery and
the shuttle has cleared the tower
[Music]
so as you can see it's quickly did that
and now we're going to do another of
these surveys at least
three okay to do this okay
confirm this uh you know it doesn't
matter
and do that survey okay once you've done
at least
three surveys you need to do at least
three three
now mcts and it's online
so now congratulations
you will get the humongous hacks once
you go public
you'll get the among us hacks
immediately now
immediately you get the among us house
immediately immediately now right now
among us hacks
now okay so i hope you enjoy imposter
every time
okay you get glitches hacks anything
anything
you want mod menu yeah it's the mod menu
okay
and poster every time and you control
your friends and you can have fun
but make sure to do that survey so