hey what's going on guys it's uh it's
furry gamers against trump here and i
have a i'm very excited today you know
i'm usually angry for these videos but
i'm happy today because i have my new
game to show off it's called echo 2 and
fan game of echo 1 okay let me just read
it out for you warning this visual novel
has racism
sexism homophobia please click off click
off the video if you're prone to trigger
warnings but i have dealt with it so
much with my discord server which you
should click right now um you should go
and link in description uh six years
after the adventures of echo one chase
we play as chase the new boyfriend
basically if you don't know um chase i
used to used to date uh michael rogers
younger brother michael rogers michael
roger used to be the younger brother of
chaser uh that's uh michael rogers
younger brother leo okay and michael
rogers uh
and now chase is now dating michael
rogers and my boyfriend uh timmy comes
in okay and that's
me and that's michael rogers but michael
rogers is me
that's my that's my youtube character my
youtube character and that's me michael
rogers and timmy's dating michael rogers
which is me i'm michael rogers
so i'm glad that we clear that out of
the way and that's michael rogers
younger brother leo okay and leo
is a [ __ ] troll he believes that the
election was stolen like a [ __ ] idiot
so
um yeah so michael rogers and chase has
to save him so here's
now you want some gameplay you know now
you're hyped up okay and i i made this
okay so it's based off the game okay so
you start up the game like this
oh [ __ ] okay
oh my god i ruined everything okay so
um it's my game furry gamers against
trump and that's michael
rogers and that's
my youtube and that's my boyfriend uh
tiffy and that's michael rogers younger
brother and that's michael rogers if you
didn't know i need to
make sure because he's very important
the game michael rogers which is
actually my self-answer so here's uh
this thing i couldn't figure out how to
stretch it out so it just warns you not
to steal my game because i hate
copyright infringement i'm a small indie
game
game developer do not steal my game and
i will sue you
i can't do that actually
you think i can't you think you'll get
away with it do not steal my game do not
steal my logo
it's real and it's 20 21 and since you
left chase racism is destroying it okay
well you save him and i ask you will you
save him will you save him from racism
okay michael rogers younger brother will
you save michael rogers younger brother
okay of course i'll save him i'm a fine
antifa okay and he says i am antifa and
it's january 2021 and if you don't know
in three days very bad things happen
very bad things happen not so good
horrible
um our election is attempted
uh donald trump wants to uh
be uh hitler in chief i mean he was the
past four years yes he's michael is a
christian controller
michael rogers is me i i think i have
become a christian i have become a
christian and i want to talk about that
later on in another video but i am a
christian me michael rogers so i am a
christian but this is chase okay so
um
yeah and she he hates his mom because
he's a dumb [ __ ] but me michael rogers
i realized that my mom's like
not as bad as i said and i kind of want
to take back some things i said about it
in previous videos but my mom's not that
bad and i didn't figure out how to
change this name my name's not tj ignore
that ignore that
my name's not tj his name is michael
rogers i couldn't figure out how to put
michael rogers
in there so
yeah i i it took a long time to make
this actually
you know it's a lot of writing you no
one really appreciates how much writing
and effort goes into visual novels a lot
of writing and effort oh it's a lot of
work honestly and i do this
i don't do this with money i don't do
this for money i do this for you i do it
for the soul i do it just for you just
for my final antifa's and i know i have
a lot of trolls who don't appreciate my
efforts and all i say is [ __ ] off
i don't need it i don't need this [ __ ]
[ __ ] you
and this is me
uh michael rogers
and some people say he looks very
similar to michael rogers younger
brother well doesn't that make sense
they're brothers
doesn't that make sense you know why
would they well you think they look
different
uh yeah i had a hard life with
depression
yeah
and
yeah it was getting to him and
yeah
and i look over to my boyfriend who is a
person of color yeah i'm dating chase
that's me
michael rogers
sorry for having white privilege michael
rogers
it is my duty to be your boyfriend i am
sorry for my privilege michael rogers
it is my duty to be your boyfriend for
the pain that has happened when you are
poor poc and still are because
people of color have suffered through a
lot of pain in this country every day
every day
and trolls they don't appreciate that
but michael rogers
and chase realize it michael rogers and
it's not tj it's michael rogers i don't
know how to remove that
thank you but does not heal the use of
slavery and racism that is
true and i'm heart and i'm horrified by
that
yeah yeah you should be a pair of
parents for your whiteness
and then the cracker uh capitalism
shitty people as [ __ ] break because
capitalism and wants things to break so
they make more money
no no
yeah capitalism
uh and he said about capitalism
oh [ __ ] uh oh i don't know how to remove
that jenna is not actually in this game
i'm gonna remove it and i'm gonna make
it uh timmy because my boyfriend my
my boyfriend is like that okay and me as
michael rogers you know i'm the big
muscle bar man but you know he doesn't
understand that
okay
um
yeah i think um
all right um i i hope everyone enjoyed
that little gameplay video
yeah and i have some comments here it's
just real life now i i don't know why
they don't understand but no it is
actually science fiction it can happen
this is if you reality shift
reality shifting which i have been doing
these past couple of months actually
i've been trying to reality shift echo
so i've been reality shifting where me
michael rogers and this is a part of my
reality shift vision
this is i should probably edit this and
put that in i haven't mentioned it this
is part of my reality shift vision of me
chase
and michael rogers younger brother leo
so
me michael rogers um
this is just my vision it's like a
visionary
and this is this is my dashboard i i put
it up like a
uh july 4th and look i'm getting a lot
of downloads
i mean you know i mean who wouldn't want
to download this great game
so um i hope i and by the way when i
upload this i better see this spike the
[ __ ] up
okay and if you want to help me uh fund
fund this you know because this isn't
this isn't free this takes a lot of time
and effort it's a lot of hard work you
can uh name your own price you know you
can give me a couple of dollars but i
better not see a 14 or an 88 in that
a 14 or an 88 i will i will refund your
money
i do not not see not money a 14 or an 88
i want none of that
no 13 or 50. no no no those numbers if i
see those numbers even single numbers i
will reject it i will not take nazi
money no no no nazis no nazis no nazis
no nazis no nazis no nazis no no no
nazis we don't accept nazi money no
nazis furry gamers against trump is
anti-nazi
[Music]
wow his hair looks like corn
okay and we came back
[Music]